Hello friends, in this video we are going to talk
about five companies
which have seen recent news last week,
so in the coming week,
a momentum down side can be seen in this, so in the coming week, along with
this stock, we will also
see the best entry point and target of
that stock, what could be its target in the long term or short term, so let's
move ahead and talk, before moving ahead,
if you have not subscribed to this channel then
please subscribe
and do not forget to like the video, so let's first
talk about the first stock, the
name of the first stock is SBI Bank, which has received
a tax notice from the Income Tax Department,
so if we can see in this, we can see that we can
see a decline in the coming days,
so we can see our entry in that decline,
where we can find a tree in it,
so let's see, this is the chart of SBI Bank
and you must be seeing that this is its
strong resistance
and this is its strong resistance and if you
look at the entry, you will see that here it has faced
resistance once, it has faced resistance twice, it has faced
resistance for the third time  It
gave it a breakout and then it is testing the same point,
so this is a principle of change policy
that the
point which acts as resistance, later on
becomes the support, so if we
talk about entry, then this level is a range of 20,
21 to 21 to
22.50, if you find this stock
in the range of 2 to 22 dopa, then it can be a
good entry point for it and you
can take it with ₹ and its
targets are coming out,
you can keep your first target at this ₹, but if you
want to hold for long term, then its
first target is coming out
after ₹, if it crosses 22, then its first
target is coming out as 8 and the
second target is coming out between 70 to 7,
so note both these targets
and pay attention to ₹, if
any daily candle closes below this, then it is
very good for you to exit from this stock.  If you want to
hold it then this
48 and 7 75 can be your target, its
best entry point is
if you find it in the range of 2 22.50 then it can be a
good entry point and the
second entry point can be if it does
not come in this range and from here
its price is ₹ 20 paise and from here turning around,
if this stock closes the daily candle
above ₹ then here also you
can make an entry by hitting the entry slot of that candle, the first target is the
same 48 and the second from 7, so here if you
want, between 70 to 5 can be a good
profit zone but do
not book the entire quantity because the stock
still has the potential to go very high, so if
[music]
we move ahead, mu fas before moving ahead let
us tell you that this way does not give any kind of
buying or selling recommendation,
so after watching this video, do some
research related to this stock, so let's
move ahead and  Talking about the second Mu Fas, Mu
Fas has acquired Bar Micro Finance
at 36, whose total
cost is around 10 crores and the
shares traded in it are 2 lakh equity
shares, so this is news related to it and
its total share holding has increased
to 63.86, so
what is market acquisition, so this is a market
transfer transaction or acquisition settlement
mutual agreement term between two parties,
if two parties make a mutual agreement
then you can do market acquisition or transaction,
in this neither the cling corporation will be
involved nor the stock exchange will be involved, there is
no involvement of both of them,
you can make your
own agreement, in this you can
transfer gift, you can transfer
shares, you can transfer legacy,
then you can do shifting of security between
client and sub-broker, this is also included in
transactions in unlisted securities, you
can also do transactions in unlisted securities, like Bal Star Micro Fund
is not listed and  Finance is listed,
you can see both of these, so this is an online market
transaction and moving ahead, if we
talk about the entry and exit of this stock, then
you can see that
if you see its strong resistance, then
its strong
resistance is coming out from 508, so either this
can be the first entry, but if it
closes above the telly candle, then you
can create a position in it by hitting the low of that telly candle and today's
target that will come out will be
0000 and if we talk about the minimum target, then
rupees will come out and if we
talk about another entry point of this, then one entry of
this stock at this level, if a down call is
seen from here and you will find it somewhere here, or
come like this and then its second entry point will be
1435, if this stock is found in the range of 1435 to 1440, then
this can be its best
entry point because you can see that the
stock has given resistance once and has given it the second
time, then it has broken it, so
if you are buying this stock  If
after breaking it comes in this range then you can see that
this zone can be its best entry point, so that is why I am saying that if there is
any decline in it in the short term,
if after falling it
gets in the range of 35 and 4, in the same
range where it had taken resistance, then
you
can make an L in it and its target here
you will have an L, if we talk about L, then you
can keep L in Mu Finance,
if the daily candle closes below 1400 to 00, then
you can exit from it, otherwise it gets
Rs 1435 and 40, then you can
make an entry in it and target it at 1600, then target of 00
and then hold it till 000, for the
long term its long term
target is coming out to be 000, so then let
us talk about the next company, the
name of the next company is Reli Power and this is the chart of Reli Power, if we
talk about it then you will see in it that for the
last few days this momentum has been
Momentum was being seen for two weeks,
before that a good fall
was seen in it, so if we
talk about its entry, then where
can the entry be made in it, then the first entry
can be made in its breakout, second entry is the one which has
given its breakout, if it
tests it again then one entry
can be made at this, two entries are coming out in this, so we will
talk about both the entries, first
entry if we talk about it, then this
entry is in the
range of 24 to, right now this stock is
running at 85 paise, so if this stock
gets in this key then it will be its
best entry and we can place it and
its targets which are coming out, the targets are coming out
very big, so the first
target will be 8, second 8 and
thirdly this stock has the potential to double your money to
in the coming few months, so you can hold it
and the second entry point which we are
talking about, so if this stock keeps moving from here,
if one its closing
daily or weekly closing, if this  If you
get a green candle above 22, if it closes
with good volume, then the volume should also
be good. If a
breakout comes with good volume,
then it can be relied upon,
otherwise it will
fail on less volume.
So you
can make an entry by taking the low of this candle. The targets will
remain the same at 38, 48 and 59, so it can be made in this
and 59 is a strong
resistance for it, you can see because
it has a
range of 15, it took support once,
took support a second time,
took support a third time, then
when it broke the support a fourth time, this point started
acting as its resistance. So if it
hits this range of 9 again at 100, then there
is a 100% chance that selling may be seen in it.
A little, not much,
you can book a small profit here.
You may have 100 lots lying around,
so you can book 30 to 40 lots in this. The
rest you  You can hold it at 60, 50, 60.
Otherwise, if it again breaks out at 59, then
you can again increase your entry and
increase your position. So, this was
my relative power related view, there was
no buying or selling recommendation, so keep this in mind this time
and do your research
in this stock only because right now its fundamentals are
not that good. If you look at the fundamentals, then it is
gradually improving in the
fundamentals, so you can make a tree in it. So, let's
talk about our next stock.
Its name is Karnataka Bank.
Karnataka Bank has an allotment of share
capital of Rs
600 crore under CPSE. So, what is
EPEP? This is a way for a listed company to raise capital without having to
submit legal paperwork to the
market. This is a way for a listed company to
raise capital for its
expansion and business expansion. If it
wants, it can
finance it through banks. All these companies had devised a
method for this
that they can raise
funds through you.  You
can deal with your business expansion finance by raising funds and
with this Karnataka Bank has made an agreement to distribute its general insurance
product to its distributor bank customers,
so these are its two news Karnataka Bank stocks, we will
talk about both the stocks, ICICI
Lobby and Karnataka Bank, so let's go,
you must be seeing this is the chart of Karnataka Bank
and right now
it is going on, its closing is available and if
we talk, you must be seeing that
consolidation started in it around 2007,
which ended in March 2023,
a breakout was seen in it in March 2023, since then
this stock has been going up, so
this is its monthly chart, you must be
looking at Karnataka Bank, so we are talking about
it because right now this stock is in a rally, so if it is
consolidating here,
if this stock gives a breakout from here,
then by consolidating above 80, then
you can make an entry in it, otherwise if we
talk about its best entry point, then
you are looking at  The activity has started and there is a breakout, so
testing is still pending in this too. So
if we talk about testing this, if the
stock comes for testing, if after
breaking it, you will be
watching the chart, you will see the pattern in it, so
if there is a breakout, then you
can wait for this range,
if this stock gets in the range of 175, then
this will be its best entry point and
this is a multi-year breakout, approximately 17, 16, 16
is a 1-year breakout, so this stock which
you are seeing is 4 to 5x, then
you can assume it because any
stock, whether it is long term or
short term, may take two and a half years to come, so
because the
financials are very good, the fundamentals are good,
you can hold it for long
term, so if there is a breakout of 16, 17 years, then it can
save your money, you
can buy Reliance, there was a breakout of LR, so
it showed a good rally and saved the investor
's money.  45 was given, so this is a
breakout of 17 years, so a good
rally can be seen in this too, if all its companies are
doing business in this manner and continue to do so, then
good moments can be seen in this, so
we were talking about its
entry, so if
[sangeet]
gets in the range of y, then it will be its best
point, otherwise it cuts here and
gives a breakout of y or 300, even then the daily
candle should close if there is no high volume,
then
this pattern is seen, after breaking down,
if this stock gets in the range of 165 to 175,
then you can make it,
and if we talk about L in this, then you
can keep 0, if the daily candle closes
below 0, if the red candle, then you will
exit from this stock because then its
structure will become very bad
and if you look at this very point,
we are talking about this level,
if it gives a breakout below 0, then you
will see that it will break the swing, so there will be a
negative in it.  Once the structure is formed,
you can exit from it. If we talk about
its targets, then the targets are very big.
In this, the first target, if you get an A here, then
your first target will be 50. The second
target which is coming out is 50 and the
third target which is
coming out is 4020. You
can keep this target at 5080. The
second target which is coming out is 350
and the third target is
40 and the fourth target is 500. This was about
Karnataka Bank and let's
talk further.
In this,
you were seeing consolidation since 2021. This
point was hit first, then selling was
seen in it. Then when it was hit for the second time,
a good selling was seen. So this
16 70 range, which was 16 to 1600 to 1620,
acted as a good resistance.
But you must be seeing that this is a bud chart
and you will see that with this good volume, a
good volume and a good green candle,
it counted  And above that, this
is its weekly chart of ICI Lambda, and you must be
looking at it,
it has been trading above this for the past two to six weeks
and is also sustaining, so if we
talk about its entry point, then if this stock
's first entry point will be if
it again
gets in the range of 1600 5 605, then you
can make an entry in it and what will be the SL,
you can keep the SL of 1500 and if we
talk about the target, the target in this is 000
00, two, the
target is coming out in this and if we
talk about its second entry, then if this stock
breaks this level,
if it closes the daily candle above it,
then also you can make an entry in it, the
target will remain the same and the SL which will break the same candle,
you can either buy 00L by hitting the SL of 1736, but this SL will become very big, so
if you break the range of 1736,
this range of 34 or 74
You can make an entry in it by making the low of the candle which breaks out of 36 as the asset, the
target will be yours
00 It should have two long term targets,
this was my video about the penis, but if you
liked this video then do not forget to like this video,
thank
you